

#### CONTACT

- Pogor, Jawa Barat 16730
- mrandiiw@gmail.com
- + 62 896 0587 7681
- in www.linkedin.com/in/mrandiw

## SKILLS

- •••• Software Development
- •••• Coding & Scripting
- •••• Debugging & Troubleshooting
- •••• Design Architecture Application
- •••• Testing & Documentation
- •••• Well Self Management
- •••• Good Team Work

## TRAINING/COURSE/ ACHIEVEMENT

- Google's Go (golang) Programming Language
- Working with Microservices in Go (Golang)
- The Complete Guide to Becoming a Software Architect
- Microservices Architecture The Complete Guide
- HackerRank Certificates Go (Basic)

# **ANDI WIBOWO**

## SR BACK END DEVELOPER

## ABOUT ME

I am a programmer currently focusing on developing backend applications. In my work career for last 8 years or so I have been working as Backend developer with expertise in Go and PHP also in framework like Laravel, Codeigniter, etc. Has Worked in both monolithic and microservices architecture and I am very comfortable in both of them.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Back End Developer

Rebelworks | July 2019 - Present

- Design, Develop and Maintain Applications as a Back End Developer.
- Create Web API for DBO Salesman App using Golang for Microservices.
- Create DBO CMS Applications using Laravel frameworks.
- Lead Technical Problem in Project DBO Toko App Application.

## Fullstack Developer

Antavaya Tour | December 2016 - July 2019

 Create Antavaya Website Version 2 and Antavaya Management System ERP, Maintenance and Create New Features And Modules on Antavaya development websites as Riset and Development Team.

## Fullstack Developer

PT. Bahtera Informatika | May 2014 - October 2016

Working on pre-existing projects, Creating Websites,
Implementing Coding, Fixing Bugs using PHP Framework
Codelgniter & MySQL. Testing using PHPUnit, selenium IDE.

## EDUCATION

## STMIK Dharma Negara

Sarjana Komputer (S.Kom) | 2014 - 2018

## SMK Wikrama Bogor

Software Engineering | 2011 - 2014

#### TRAINING/COURSE/ ACHIEVEMENT

- Amazon EC2 Masterclass (Auto Scaling & Load Balancer)
- SOLID Principles: Introducing Software Architecture & Design
- VETA (Vocational Educational And Training Authority)
- Certificate of Competency

#### TECHNOLOGY SUMMARY

- Go
- PHP
- Javascript
- Laravel
- Codelgniter
- JQuery
- Vue Js
- Node Js
- React Js
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Redis
- GIT
- RabbitMQ
- Kafka
- REST API
- Web Socket
- Docker
- AWS
- Google Analytic
- API Gateway

#### PROJECTS PORTOFOLIO

## DBO | Depoguna Bangunan Online

Rebelworks | 2019 — Now

- Internal Website Management
- Back End Developer
- Full Stack Developer

## DBO | Salesman APP

Rebelworks | 2019 — Now

- Mobile App
- Back End Developer
- Full Stack Developer

## TINC | Telkomsel Innovation Center

Telkomsel | 2020

- Web Portal
- Full Stack Developer

#### Tinc Hub

Telkomsel | 2021

- Web Portal
- Full Stack Developer

## Management Cuti Online Antavaya

Antavaya Tour | 2018

- Internal Website Management
- Full Stack Developer

## <u>Antavaya Transport</u>

Antavaya Tour | 2017

- Web Portal
- Full Stack Developer

## **Anta Umroh**

Antavaya Tour | 2017

- Web Portal
- Full Stack Developer

## <u>Antavaya Website</u>

Antavaya Tour | 2017

- Web Portal
- Full Stack Developer

## Peraturan.go.id

PT Bahtera Informatika | 2015

- Web Portal
- Full Stack Developer

## <u>Aplikasi Sistem Database Pemasyarakatan (SDP)</u>

PT Bahtera Informatika | 2014

- Internal Website Management
- Back End Developer

## PROJECTS PORTOFOLIO

## Gadis | Gadis.co.id

Gadis | 2022 — 2022

- Website Management
- Back End Developer
- Full Stack Developer

# IDIS | Aplikasi Integrated Discipline

IDIS | 2022 — 2022

- Website Management
- Back End Developer
- Full Stack Developer

## Femina | femina.co.id

Femina | 2022 — 2022

- Website Management
- Back End Developer
- Full Stack Developer